tigercricket.com.bd 2015-11-23

# Website Partner

                                                                      Website Partner
About Tigercricket.com.bd
Tigercricket.com.bd is the Official Website of Bangladesh Cricket Board.
Bangladesh Cricket Board (BCB) is the governing body of cricket in Bangladesh and is
recognized under the National Sports Council (NSC) Act 1974, having its Head Office in Sher-
e- Bangla National Cricket Stadium, Dhaka 1216, Bangladesh.
In partnership and in accordance of the Policy and Guideline of Bangladesh Cricket Board
(BCB), tigercricket.com.bd is designed, developed, hosted, managed and operated by
Solutions 360 Ltd (STL), the Digital Media Service Provider of BCB. However, BCB holds the
Exclusive Ownership of the contents of the website , including but not limited to, Intellectual
Property Right, Trademark, Copyright etc.
The website is managed and operated in full compliance of all related rules and regulations
of the People’s Republic of Bangladesh.
This privacy policy explains what information we collect about you, how we use it, and the
necessary steps taken to keep it secure. We also explain your rights and how to contact us.
This website may contain links to other websites which are provided for your convenience.
We are only responsible for the privacy practices and security of this site. We recommend
that you check the privacy and security policies and procedures of each and every other
website that you visit.
By using this website and giving personal information to us, if and where applicable, you
therefore confirm your consent to us and our respective partners about collecting and using
this personal information in accordance with the terms set out in this policy.
CHILDREN
If you are under 16, you will need the permission of your parent or guardian before
registering on our website(s) and we will require your parent or guardian to confirm that
they have given permission. We may ask for their contact details so that we can check that
they have done so and may carry out checks to confirm that the details you have given us
are correct.
We normally only send newsletters and offers and opportunities to children where their
parent or guardian has given consent to them being sent. Your parent or guardian can
change their mind at any time (see ‘Newsletters, Offers and Opportunities’ below).

THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
In order to provide you with the services you require, tigercricket.com.bd will collect
personal information about you from our website, telephone conversations, emails and
written and verbal communications. These will include, for example, your name, address,
email address, phone number and details that are relevant to the service(s) in which you are
interested. Occasionally we may ask for date of birth, for example, where the service you
require has age related restrictions.
We may supplement the information that you provide with other information that we
obtain from our dealings with you or which we receive from other organisations.
Information about other people
If you provide information to us about any person other than yourself, you must ensure that
they understand how their information will be used and that you are authorised to disclose
it to us, and to consent to its use on their behalf, before doing so.
IP addresses
In order to understand how users use our website and services, we may collect IP addresses.
Cookies
In accordance with the common industry practice with many other website operators, we
may use standard technology called 'cookies' on this site. Cookies are small pieces of
information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive and they are
used to record how you navigate this website on each visit.
Our cookies are used to enable us to develop our website to reflect our customers interests
and by noting who has seen which pages, properties and advertisements (including click
throughs from emails), how frequently particular pages are visited and to enable us to
determine the most popular areas of our website. We may use cookies to enrich your
experience of using the website by allowing us to tailor what you see to what we have
learned about your preferences during your visits to the site. Sometimes we use third
parties services such as Google Analytics and they may use cookies on our behalf in order to
provide their services.
You may get cookies (including Flash cookies) from our sponsors and advertisers if you click
on their links or adverts. You should check their privacy and security policies to understand
how they use these.
Flash cookies
Adobe uses a particular type of cookie called a ‘Local Shared Object’. Typically, these will be
collected if you watch a video which uses Adobe’s Flash media player.

Preventing use of cookies
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to
prevent cookies being stored. With experience, you can usually choose to switch off all
cookies or to allow only certain ‘trusted’ sites to place cookies.
Please note, if you do turn cookies off, this will limit the service that we are able to provide
to you and may affect your user experience (for example, you may have to manually re-type
your usernames and passwords each time you visit our website)
HOW WE WILL USE YOUR INFORMATION
All personal information that we obtain about you and/or any other person whose details
you provide will be recorded, used, and protected by us in accordance with current data
protection legislation, our Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy. We will primarily
use the personal information:
       for registration, membership and general administration (including verification,
        vetting, security checking, issuing tickets, passes and permits as appropriate)
       to provide the services you request from us
       to communicate with you in the event that any services requested are unavailable or
        if there is a query or problem with your requests
       for record keeping purposes
       to carry out market research so that we can improve the services we offer
       to track and analyse activity on our website
       to create an individual profile for you so that we can enhance your user experience,
        to understand and respect your preferences and to provide newsletters and details
        of relevant offers and opportunities where you have agreed to receive them
Disclosing your personal information
In order to provide our products and services, we may, occasionally, appoint other
organisations to carry out some of the processing activities on our behalf. These may
include, for example, technology hosts, printing companies and mailing houses. In these
circumstances, we will ensure that personal information is properly protected and that it is
only used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

NEWSLETTERS, OFFERS AND OPPORTUNITIES
We and the Sponsors, Advertisers and Partners may contact you and/or any person whose
information you provide to us to provide newsletters and to tell you and/or them about
offers and opportunities (such as match ticketing, discounts, competitions, events and
hospitality) that are available and about a range of other initiatives in a number of ways,
including by post, telephone, text/picture/video message or by email. Details of how to opt-
in to or opt-out of receiving details of offers are on relevant pages of this website.
Subscribe / Unsubscribe
You and any other person whose information you have provided to us can change
your/their mind about whether you wish to receive details of offers and opportunities at
any time by using any of the methods described or by following the instructions with each
offer you/they receive.
SECURITY
We take the security of personal information seriously. We employ security technology,
including firewalls, and Secure Socket Layers to safeguard information and have procedures
in place to ensure that our paper and computer systems and databases are protected
against unauthorised disclosure, use, loss and damage.
MONITORING
We may monitor or record telephone calls for security purposes and to improve the quality
of the services we provide to you.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy laws and practice are constantly developing and we aim to meet high standards. Our
policies and procedures are, therefore, under continual review. We may, from time to time,
update our security and privacy policies and suggest that you check this page periodically to
review our latest policy.
UPDATING AND CORRECTING INFORMATION
You may update or correct your personal information online in relevant membership areas
or by contacting us in writing or by email. Please include your name, address and/or email
address when you contact us as this helps us to ensure that we accept amendments only
from the correct person. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information
if it changes. If you are providing updates or corrections about another person, we may
require you to provide us with proof that you are authorised to provide that information to
us.
